Who dares make me leave? I'm carrying the Jiang family's heir
This is your grandson. Would you let her roam out there?
Stop pretending. At your age, how could you even get pregnant?
We're at a hospital, how could I lie? Please, Mom, son begs you
I'm ruined already, but the child is the Jiang family's only heir
In my past life, I caught my husband's affair and was killed
This life, your family will pay in blood
Xiao Lan, come wash my feet. Zhang Guifang
Don't push it. Oh, my precious son says
he wants Grandma serving him personally. If she doesn't serve well
he won't come out. He'll stay in there, let's see who panics
Honey
Honey, calm down, careful with the baby
You're only spared because you carry the Jiang heir. Sweep away... No, wrong
Something's off. Jiang Chengao's look isn't one for a daughter-in-law
Gently, I'm carrying your heir inside. Don't press on it